we'll talk about that stuff yo ya
welcome welcome you guys this is some
pipe this is yo all right all right
first off we some caffeine so let's go
go into the fridge one of the common
fridge you know I get real hype for this
this is amazing product launch
we're launching a USB the a two mini
beat no no no not don't worry I wouldn't
launch that what's up uh sure bro a sure
bio what's log - well log - in base - I
believe is 1 because 2 to the 1 is - all
right we don't have any to give Benny
got T all right we got some some pure
leaf tea Antonio I didn't ignore you
and E is not here welcome welcome
welcome
alright what's Ln - I don't know that
mod C so if E is uh know what he is
he is like - I'm not gonna embarrass
myself I'm just gonna import numpy MP
dot ye yeah 2.7 all right I was gonna
say two points an X that's embarrassing
that I don't know what he is by pi
3.14159265 three five nine seven nine I
let's go we are in general with the
YouTube yeah well in general with the
YouTube what's the news we got news
today we got news today yo Chris you
want to hit that button
do it alright alright ah
oh that's the product you can't show you
that what's the derivative of e to the X
the derivative the ito yes I believe is
e to the X and the integral of e to the
X is also e to the X that's why you DX
is so awesome everybody should use
they'll use and not rel use all right
we're just gonna give everyone a minute
to come in here we're at a hundred
people that's nice got this on
we're let's put that on Twitter we don't
want anybody to miss anything
drink some tea we got it we got to be
calm I know I know it's it's exciting
let's go dark mail let's go uh uh put on
my nicest sweat pants today I got my
Hyundai with small park not rel UL use
better than Relius nice and smooth no
sometimes you want values but envision
models all you seem to work better we
ask you to test on this that's why we
use L use in our vision Bo and really
use in our heads G on guys are great but
guys this what if it doesn't even have
to do with young guy what if you all got
tricked you know and we're launching
commas sneakers what's happening this
dream we're launching products and
there's an S on there it's plural def
cons cancel don't know y'all who wants
to have Underground Def Con we'll call
it make Def Con cool again I'll put it
on all right you guys some CTF problems
will be sick make Def Con cool again
sneakers grads would be profitable thank
you thank you
we're actually last month was not
profitable off our obvious reasons we
don't have to discuss but this month
we're looking profitable again we hired
a great production engineer we're gonna
go back we're gonna look at the
production facilities a bit today it's
gonna be pretty good idea oh my favorite
artist I don't know any artists
who's a great artist a good artist Elon
Musk
Hockman um what's my opinion the lottery
can hypothesis this is a nice dream oh
man I forgot the s in the plural all
right what we're gonna go to the title
guy and we're gonna give the title guy a
week of unpaid time off cuz you did a
bad job on the title uh no I didn't
watch new Elon and Joe Rogan uh Banksy
I've heard a Banksy I don't know who
else who else a visual art visual arts
kind of hard these days who do I like
the world is a beautiful place I'm no
longer afraid to die there are artists
Shinigami
I listen to who was it the Dixie Chicks
song this morning it's pretty good bear
philosopher plain EJ you choose like got
look you feel like you feel like a
certain like when you read it you know
you feel like you feel like strong and
powerful and then you read Heidegger and
you're like what's this guy saying I
have no idea man being in time his go
links a passing Python in the future I
don't know why not make it a lot easier
for people buying all compiled what do
you say what are you saying what do you
want make a PR and github that's what I
like to hear
that's the way to interact that is the
future um you believe in something what
do you believe in whoa whoa whoa panel
who's heard of the pan of Jumonville all
right all right I think it's I think
it's time let's get that up that let's
get the view count up to up to 200 and
then and then we'll really start this
stuff out
oh yes yes we are looking good
where is your order it should have
definitely shipped all right where are
200 people let's go
so we're gonna start with a cute little
product we're gonna start with our
smallest of the products xx xx 979
Hyundai bro absolutely boy not I'd love
that but this isn't young guy this whoa
Hyundai car harness whoa whoa whoa what
are you guys doing whoa we're starting
with this it's really small so I'm gonna
bring it nice and close to the thingy so
you guys can see it you see this this is
a comma key okay so use your story you
adventure it off of release - you wanted
to try the latest mods you are cutting
edge so cutting edge in fact that you
bricked your comet oh you can brick the
coma - if you're right bad panda
firmware um but no fear if you have a
comma key a comma key makes your comma -
almost unbreakable if you really do bad
stuff you can still technically break it
you can fix it if you take it apart but
this makes your comment to effectively
unbreakable all you have to do take your
comma key plug it into the back of your
car - right there and then when you hold
this button down the Panda goes into DFU
mode so this is a comma key uh there are
99 dollars and they're available right
now at shop.com Adani I slash products
right here with a nice little story
apparently they only have one picture
this is a comma key yeah $99 damn I know
yeah comma keys are expensive but you
know do you want to solder all those
little tiny USB shits no you don't so
that's a comma key a comma key is like a
pan to pull off but it's for the comma -
and also potentially
for future products with the OE DC
connector how does it come and get power
with the key you just plug it in right
here you plug in a second USB over here
so I can just plug this guy in right
here and there you go yes small price to
pay if you brick it alright so that's a
comm this is just a normal comma - let's
move on to our next product and that's
right over here this product here is the
Panda jungle alright so we've had to
build you know what maybe before we
announce the jungle we're gonna go take
a lot a look it's $2.99 it's $2.99 it's
a good price let's go take a look at
some stuff that we've built yeah yeah
we're on Warren live stream right now
yeah iced coffee alright welcome oh
they're gonna boot up now welcome
we have 272 people alright but I'm just
showing off the jungles aren't they
ready to go all they're firing up right
now there's gonna be cool this is how we
test the comet to us before we send them
to you they're actually really well
tested now and each comma two is powered
back here by a pain panting rig oh yeah
yeah twelve one you want to show them
the power supply yeah we to put heavy
gauge wires for each panda because they
were overheating you couldn't burn your
fingers on the water that's some nice
thick wire yeah all right so we're
connecting to them right now yeah yeah
they're all gonna start right now this
is what you can do with your panda
jungle this is what's possible if you
read along if you write a lot of code oh
wow that's crazy
floor gang yeah floor gang yeah so they
just they just will come up and test all
through the convenient panda jungle
which can be yours for the low price of
$2.99 let's go take a look at it oh by
the way also
we sold a thousand pandas to an unnamed
buyer for 69 thousand dollars they're
purchasing a Killa panda or first ever
kill a panda so that's boxed up ready to
go the other bit of exciting news is if
you buy a comet to see these comet twos
they are unclaimed one of these can be
yours right now we have 40 in stock
ready to ship on Monday so now is the
perfect time to buy a comet - and
there's gonna be many more comet oohs
where that one came from as you can see
by we are the world's largest
refurbisher about Lego phones yeah so
that is that let's go back to our
computer and let's take a look at the
other product all right go back to shop
here scroll down go to the developer
shop down here you'll find the Panda
jungle what's better than a debug board
pandas in a jungle by the way you can
plug in up to six comma twos in one
panda jungle one two tres cuatro Cinco
seis that's a crazy amount so you can do
that with oh and the jungle was of
course for sale for two hundred and
ninety-nine dollars so so far we've
announced the comma key right here
perfect for I'm breaking your comma - if
you do stupidly brick it and also the
Panda jungle you're about to buy a comma
- congratulations now is absolutely the
time to smash that buy button get a
comment - you'll be like wow I bought a
comma - I'm so happy all right how many
jungles can you run in series as many
jungles as you can buy
we're running a whole wooden rack full
of jungles that's a whole like I don't
even know man that's a whole South
America back there
alright so let's plug this wire in
I don't know what a GI means what's the
common jungle I'd say the Panda jungle
so for example your comma to indoors
it's not a very expensive way you don't
have to make sure that switch yeah
there's also a switch to get the power
and you can see that it's booting out so
there we go the Panda jungle can you
connect a jungle to a jungle absolutely
you can connect a jungle to a jungle six
times actually this is the control port
for the jungle which you can connect to
a computer the jungle has basically a
panda on board we're gonna open source
the firmware probably later today maybe
Monday I has four can buses on it as a
panda it's got some nice voltage
regulator you can trigger ignition here
it's got some some LEDs that show you
yes we shipped to India we ship
everywhere the common jungle looks so
nice panda jungle buy your panda jungle
right now
okay 324 people let's let's take a
minute and let's go through our
whiteboard I cleaned off things that
were secret on the whiteboard notice
that the secrets have been removed but
kama has come a long way and you know we
really appreciate having all of you here
on the journey with us
they bought white pandas they bought a
lot of white banners one of our goals is
million dollar July you guys will be
hearing a lot more about million dollar
July you know this is the other this is
the other crazy thing notice how our
competition is wilting look at zukes
right okay I'm not talking about the
competition we're talking about open
pilot 1.0 look at all these things
I'm talking about all of this stuff
level 5 platform profitable q3 and q4
noted failure of others disengagement
analysis you do all the things that
we're gonna buy with all our crazy new
amount of money whoa timeline for the
comma three no one said anything about
the comma three though there is one
other big product announcement there is
one other big product announcement today
but we're gonna we're gonna we're gonna
we're gonna can we get to 350 people
before we do the next product
announcement Oh a six might happen a lot
of stuff might happen brought up common
your recent job interview and murders
that a good thing that a good thing I
don't know can I tell but this is a
common key if you guys don't have a
common key you can buy one for 99
dollars this is a panda jungle you guys
don't have a pan jungle you can actually
order it right now let's see if
anybody's ordered any of this stuff
murder killed in a good way oh that's
great that's great
yo wait sale
those are going crazy waste sales are
going crazy how many pandas and jungles
have we sold that's all I'm interested
in right now pandas and jungler I don't
think we've sold any pandas and jungles
oh you just bought that oh whoa whoa
whoa I don't know where you heard about
that alright we're almost at 350 people
this here is the key to my Hyundai
Sonata I've been driving it she undies
are going to be the best car for open
pilot and in order to support that we're
launching the Hyundai harness now now
you say oh this is a harness how
exciting could that be gross the shunned
eye harness is actually five harnesses a
B C D and E and there's an F G and H
coming soon that aren't ready
Hyundai is a terrible manufacturer and
makes every harness different yeah so if
you have an a harness you need this
wannabe harness you need this wanna see
harness don't worry this is conveniently
done with our compatibility flow and I
bring you live
[Laughter]
so there's some fun as I will just work
out of the box is not a 20/20 it's
supported community supported by the
comma - no issue you there but the
hardware teams not great job checking a
bunch of these different cars like this
is a giant list and all these cars will
be checked so let's say we wanted to get
a cone a harness you'll get the second
screen that says that you probably built
in a movie camera I'm gonna say yes and
there's a smooth page that's likely
candidate and just because it's not
supported by open pilot yet doesn't say
community support it but we still do
sell the harness so you could click buy
it adds the right harness to your cart
we have the ones we have the ones in
bold that are yeah yeah we can go
through this that's pretty good so wow
this is we should we should uh we should
open source us yeah yeah yeah we get we
got to do this cuz this is confusing
I could scroll down and there are
some Hyundai available here as well as
some Kia's wow this is getting so long
Wow look at all those Wow yonder ice and
then there's some key as well yeah yeah
wait so someone was asking about the
Sonata 2019 oh but it is supported by
any yeah so if you do it you'll just get
out tell you what jungling Kyary if you
don't understand what the jungling key
are they aren't for you should we look
at best - yeah sure so I'm gonna post
this in the discord this just shows this
type yeah 1 2 + S which is a so either
your connector look at what wires are in
it and you'll know what Wow as well so
that's gonna go out in the discord for
people who want to check what car they
have yeah we should actually you want to
write a medium post with like links to
these things talking about what a pain
he Hyundai is and maybe encouraging
to changed I already own a comma -
Hyundai e is not listed on the car
harness shop page so go to the car
harness oh yeah by the way wait you know
not car scroll down go to harness
connector yeah by the way we've raised
the price of the harness connector to
$100 oh wait no it's not here no it's
not gonna be here you can't get the very
bottom oh I see so any car that's
unsupported you can still select at the
bottom
Hyundai e development wow that's the
biggest pain yes the biggest pain Wow
shun dies the worst
alright a dandy you just make sure it
works cuz some guys said it didn't work
alright yo Hyundai II wait is that also
at the bottom of the car harness so if
you go back to okay I don't make sense
you could of course buy that with a
black Panda if you want that too but
yeah the Hyundai is not look at this
look guys who wouldn't do this why did
they do this you know the comet team has
been working really hard to make this
possible for you guys yeah let's let's
just link those resources in discord now
if you guys are not in our discourse at
discord comedy I yeah we'll start with
that picture and then medium poster be
nice the difficulty of the Hyundai
harness I think that's a great medium
post people know that we put a real
effort into that and that's why all the
stuff is uh so he's been soo
don't take me CoA from comma pencil well
yeah I mean you know come on pencils
very important but John Knight harnesses
bring in money and we love money so yeah
we need to win that win that money so
you guys should buy those gondii
harnesses I heard about wonderful I
heard wonderful things about you know
how many people were gonna buy this so
I'm really hoping for everybody to come
to come buy this
you guys have choices you can buy an a
you can buy a B or you can buy a see you
can buy a D or you can buy an e the
discount code for the live stream is you
better buy one of these before they run
out you think we're keeping five things
in stock that's a crazy amount of things
that's as many fingers as I have and
just wait'll we launch F G and H we're
gonna have to get into toes just kidding
I know I have ten fingers all right what
else we got what else we got
that's most of the stuff we had planned
for today we're gonna go to 30 minutes
here oh man I've been playing around go
commas trying to become a we're trying
to get the comma twos to have custom
comma IME eyes let's see how my new
models coming along on the models coming
along okay losses going down that's good
any extra if you call all right all
right all right I guys we're gonna do it
I'm gonna make a discount right now this
was not part of any plans but I'm just
gonna make a discount for you guys are
you guys ready for the discounts all
right all right the discount code is
gonna be lucky yeah well do it right
here okay the discount code is going to
be live stream one and it's gonna be a
fixed amount and it's gonna save one
dollar if you know the code live stream
one $1 off your entire order and you can
only of course use this once per
customer
no limit the number of times okay you
know what we're only gonna have not
another another no I think everybody can
use this and we're gonna have it go for
the next hour let's say everybody who
gets in during the live stream you guys
can use the code live stream one to get
one dollar off your entire order that's
how generous we are commenting on a I
hear you guys save $1 right now smash
that Buy button you'll never get it
cheaper than right now save $1 until
3:00 p.m. so it ends it then at 3:00
p.m.
$1 you guys can save $1 you guys can go
donate your dollar to Doctors Without
Borders or something or whatever you
want to donate your dollar to but it's
$1 off the entire
order for everyone let's see how many
people are gonna start to use this
amazing discount code
let's get these orders and I don't know
what Mahindra Scorpio is save a dollar
everybody save a dollar I'm gonna go get
those hair dye harnesses so I can I can
caress them while we have more
livestream
yeah yeah harnesses all right let's go
over quickly everything that we launched
in today's live stream yeah save the
dollar yeah all right who's spamming hit
is spamming you are in timeout Mahindra
Scorpio I don't know what that is you're
in timeout okay we have the type a horn
type B or as well as a so much stuff so
much stuff how many people right now
I've saved a dollar you better get that
order and fast should I put a limited
number of dollars that can be saved
Wow nobody's using it we need we need
some dollar we come on spend some money
we got we got 11 orders today already
all of this stuff ships all this stuff
ships Monday so when you guys get your
order in ships by Monday talk to your
dad right now spend your stimulus check
this is a great place to spend your
stimulus check well that's some
delicious tea this is a delicious jungle
okay well we have one last jungle now it
was delicious was the best $299 I ever
spent
yes oh so is that here's economic II
don't want have another jungle right
here wins Volkswagen harness you guys
you guys we make something for you and
you just ask when's next we make
something amazing for you Hyundai
harnesses look look at the detail that
goes into this it's like that's the
connector
that's crazy stuff Dada Dada it's got a
type s connector what is the comma key
for if you break your comma - you can
unbreak it with a comma key thank you
thank you give you a shout out I'll give
you a shout out if you use the discount
code whose use the discount code
livestream one all right you know what
we want to incentivize some people to
buy some stuff so here's what we're
gonna do we're gonna blow wait people
didn't even use the code but we got new
orders we're at 14 orders now that's
crazy okay should we increase the
discount you place the order can you get
$1 back if you contact support bro bro
no you order before discount all right
all right all right all right all right
we'll give everybody we'll give
everybody $1 off but there's a $5
support fee I like that you know what
buy a meeting
you're just use the discount code wait I
don't know maybe this is just broken it
says zero use but I think it's just
broken cuz we now have 15 orders yeah I
don't know maybe Shopify is just broken
yo discount and get a dollar off
anything $1 off your entire order if
you'd like your if you'd like the
discount code retro actively added to
your stuff might I recommend purchasing
a meeting and we can do that
so for $1000 you can buy a meeting you
can also save a dollar on the meeting if
you proceed to checkout um and you use
this great discount code oh may 500
meetings not a valid discount code
anymore but if you use the discount code
livestream one you can save one dollar
that's crazy that's crazy that's the
biggest savings we've offered in a long
time II see bee
ah D and a get the whole family in here
like alphabet soup
the shirts are sold out your shirts sold
out wait we sold out of shirts nikkor we
sold out of shirts some sizes Wow
we got to get some more shirts we're
gonna do what you say oh yeah I don't
know about that I don't know if we're
gonna get that crazy nice bag look at
these we're now filtering out comma two
is that overheat stress test failed look
those ones fail we take him out we don't
ship them to you comma two is are the
highest quality they've ever been if
you're thinking about buying a comma
tube with the crazy one you know I offer
to 100 discount yet live stream one oh
nice sweet sweet bye Paul wait they got
a $19 Paul that's too cheap oh well okay
5% discount what do you think this is
you save a dollar be happy you're
googled what some a hindu Scorpio oh
it's a cool car alright um these are
more testings I kill a panda you know
did you know you could put metric
prefixes before pandas bring back the
comma vini
we're apparently out us from shirt sizes
we're gonna get more shirts in one of
these days yeah these are our values
externalization sustainability its
ability and quality not growth and not
short-term profit million-dollar July
you guys have been hearing a lot about
that we're trying to shoot for 8 million
in revenue in 2020 this is how many
years everybody thinks until we get to
level 5 self-driving so we got 225 s in
there we got some twos and threes and
fours and fives
I was the 8 a gig of Pantera tariffs and
we don't have any pandas we don't even
have a mega Panda
how many comma 2 is are we shipping each
month now about 250 I'm more than that
actually
yeah that was last month it's about 500
now
yeah check it out
kama jungle how good is open pilot bro
I'm not convinced to give a you
don't know how good it is don't all buy
it when is nissan support coming
official we have nissan support i've
streamed is your 0.75 model fix you know
we have some issues with that model well
uh we're gonna do 0 75 next week to make
sure that comes out before the hyundai
oh whoa five people have used the
discount code even know what's going on
Shopify is just weird
five people did you guys actually email
support so you can get it reg who
actively added your orders yeah um just
for the rest of this live stream you can
use the code live stream on if you don't
think $1,000 is affordable might you
consider a Tesla
we're both self driving costs is it
seven thousand or even get a comma two
for just 999 what a crazy low price we
point out how beautiful comma twos are
they're so beautiful
Hyundai support is already here Keanu my
support is already in master and we're
gonna ship that in zero 75 with chips
next week so if you order a Hyundai
harness right now by the time it gets to
you he and I support will be in open
pilot um do we support the Russian
language we're working on multi Lang
multi Lang is a requirement for open
pilot one point out um what phone is
modified so it's not really a phone
anymore we just like use the phone case
and like the phone motherboard but like
it's not it doesn't have a battery it
has a replacement front camera so we can
see in the dark it's kind of like a
bunch of phone parts you know what I
mean Elan built it what it was it what
is it Tony Stark built this in a cave
with scraps yeah bro by a comet oh
another great the testing has improved
leaps and bounds so if you buy a comma
today you're getting one that went
through a really rigorous testing that's
24 hours of non-stop perfection how much
longer will Yuans be supported if you
have a black panda you'll get a bit more
out of it if you have a white panda
going away soon if you have a gray panda
results may vary depending on your
fingerprints if you have a Black Manta
it'll be well your black banner will
continue sporty out for a while but um
yeah before that you know it's been it's
been it's been almost a year now it's
just we launched the black Panda like
nine months white panda we launched grey
pandas so long ago so white pandas are
going away
well it'll be an affordable calm
assistance don't like to comment too
little and if you don't think the comma
to is affordable guess what I have for
you I have for you a sick discount it's
called live stream one uh and you guys
can get one dollar off your entire order
Aryan stop spamming five people have
already used this incredible discount
that let's let's just pretend that
you're buying a comet too
let's let's do that right now we'll take
out this sick discount code out of our
cart you're not gonna buy a meeting the
meetings are legitimately a scam don't
buy a meeting the meetings are just you
know it's kind of like but actually sold
three meetings so why they bought the
pandas we don't ask those questions we
just sell we just sell okay ah let's say
I wanted to buy a comet too
let's say I'm buying it for my beautiful
new Hyundai Sonata 2020 which is really
a great car that's gonna be the top car
that's why it's the a harness by now it
doesn't ship with any software that's
fine I know where to get software we're
gonna hear proceed to checkout
and guys it's never been cheaper right
now to purchase a comet too because I
can use this incredible discount code
livestream one and I can save one dollar
you get one dollar off a white panda you
can get one dollar off everything with
that discount code alright let's take a
look at some of our products oh this is
a black panda
we have black pandas there in stock you
don't really want one because guess
what's inside of a comma two black
and technology that's right you know
it's right here
GPS antenna inside the mount kama tombs
are incredible futuristic technology
that you'll only be able to find right
here at shop comma dot AI so you just
plug this guy into here this is the OB
DC connector in the comment who has one
wire it gets power any data over the one
wire then you'll plug that into your
convenient harness block which is
included with the purchase of a car
harness which you buy with your comma to
you just take that guy plug it into
there and then let's say I was getting
that 2020 Sonata so I have the a harness
right here I take the a harness gives a
nice satisfying click I can write this
all in my trim and that lets my Hyundai
Sonata experience most incredible level
to self-driving this side of autopilot
and super cruise this is a bomb your
comma to broke when you dropped it why'd
you drop it
No okay oh and then you also need the
comma power so this here is a comma
power next image Ethernet wire this
provides constant power your comma to
which can put it on the comma Connect
app which if you guys haven't read my
medium post you guys should go read my
medium post about the time my car got
towed and I used comma connect I see
Honda is getting super cruzi I'll
believe that when I see it this is a
great excuse to buy another comma to
with a live stream one that's an
incredible idea too much money we've
made so far tonight how are we doing
yeah that's not that good that's not
that good you guys can do better you
guys can do better this is our total
sales for the day I believe in y'all you
can do better than that oh we sold two
comic Keys developer car harnesses those
Hyundai harnesses we got to start
selling a man you know what you guys are
better than the Subaru people though
right I believe in you
you guys buy a lot of counter harnesses
don't make me regret all the absurd
amount of work we went to to make eight
different types of Honda harnesses yes I
think I'll compile it will get
longitudinal control for the young guys
we're working on that we're pretty
excited about that how can you add a
2020 Sanada the car just go to 2020
Sanada shows up his car harness young
guy a you don't need to carry it in
Wi-Fi you just get common prime it's
included three to three months with the
comma to think the power of the phone
that there's so much power in here guys
it's been coated in Python we'll just go
to C++ free ECB you yeah I'm regretting
the discount already you know what you
know what guys discounts over discounts
are you sure you should have bought it
sooner you should have bought it sooner
five people got this incredible
livestream one discount but now the
discount is over delete discount oh we
sold 10 killed ionises wait am I just
not looking in the right place well
that's pretty amazing we've really sold
tenth hang on
yeah we bring that up I'm bringing it up
right now and chop fine let's do today
oh wait I think I was looking at the
wrong day uh car harness oh yeah whoa
yeah we're selling young guy bonuses
they're moving I mean I don't know how
you got ten or just say five I don't
even remember but we've already sold
five that's pretty good Wow so much
better the Subaru resold zero Subaru
harnesses we solve a two FCA harnesses
we're only halfway through this live
stream and Hyundai is already at full
arm you were gonna play with a $1
discount not anymore I'm sorry I'm sorry
you know you got to move fast if you
want to get that - all right we'll bring
back the discount all right all right
we're bringing the discount back all
right calm down
well I really just deleted that hard all
right all right I'll bring the discount
back all right all right I know I know I
know the only thing worse livestream the
only thing worse than missing out on a
discount is being so close I fixed
amount discount $1 applies to entire
order everybody's eligible and remember
it ends in just 25 minutes at 3:00 p.m.
$1.00 off the entire order livestream
won its back its back boys livestream
one Wow livestream one oh yeah let's
let's promote this yeah this is dill
oh I don't even know
guys this pretty good livestream thanks
for looking out for karma today's a
great day to buy with the $1 off
discount livestream one
oh well sessions are to the moon though
well there's seven people on the website
right now okay look it's sessions there
to the moon even know something
something weirds going on here eyes Ida
Pro running I'm working on something
hundred dollars off whoa what we never
do discounts like that we see you can
save $1 right now that's the best
oh yeah we're using the hexacopter yes
peter around the driver monetary model
which runs this is a big picture of a
comet to see one of these guys as a
camera the top one that's a camera right
there do $3 yes you do you showed your
discount cards no we can go through the
discount cause I don't think any of them
are that good ah
wait a second yeah some of these are
wait this just shouldn't be here right
yeah why are all these discount codes
still active whoa hang on
Wow there's all these secret discount
codes that were given to people Wow good
thing or they're limited no I think
these are mostly for so if you buy
things in bulk we'll hook you up with a
discount code if you want to buy more
than 10 of an item from the comma store
you can you know let's see last time
we've done like a real discount
oh we had discount code shirt discount
code shirt was pretty fast
ah no I'm not they're already all gone
oh yeah we sold two meetings with the
meeting discount code we sold one
meeting without a discount
yeah but wow we haven't had our real
discount a real discount a while yeah
I'll work for Yano for Labor Day Labor
Day was the last real discount yeah we
usually do Labor Day discounts hunter
dollars off no get out of here with you
hundred dollars off two hundred oh wow
no no we gave him a dollar off they
should be happy with that
I put the discount code back it's only
till 3 p.m. if you email in later if you
really before and say you want the
dollar and you ordered before 2:00 we'll
give you the dollar but if you order
after 3 no dollar for you ok we're done
talking about discount codes I know I
had a hundred dollar code all active I
don't know how that got in there it
wasn't for it wasn't for you I mean you
can look at these codes they've barely
been used by any buggin we're done
talking about discount codes but we will
quickly look at discount codes like um
so like you see these are like one
person discount codes they're not like
real the last legit discount code we had
was shirked or you could buy one item
and you would get a shirt that's why
we're out of shirts uh I regret doing
the discount so badly we're out of
shirts cuz we gave them all away for
super cheap we're using a resume we're
using an efficient map it's even better
so save a dollar right now with this
town called live stream one this is a
comic jungle this is a comic e is a
panda jungle a comma key don't plug your
common keys into here my short out your
jumble they're designed to be plugged
into comma twos like that you
look at this comma - this can be yours
for the low price my hair looks bad well
you know guys there's a little something
going on right now that's a little hard
to get a haircut
um big models going pretty well stopping
the traffic lights kind of works there's
a common to overheat not really
sometimes some people are experiencing
overheating where they leave their car
out in the Sun it takes like five
minutes to cool down we're working on
that but it doesn't overheat while
you're driving it's pretty quiet - yeah
all right let's take a deep breath let's
do a few questions well we just wait for
the sales to pour in and people to use
this incredible discount code livestream
or if you're interested in gondii
harness there's never been a better time
you can purchase this Hyundai harness oh
wow that's a lot of sales no no we have
that
got about your office's your back you
ordered a comma key excellent
you're gonna love a comma key it's a
great product chill meditation stream
Tama - yeah I don't know I mean what
else what else do you guys want to see
what is that what is the title about
today we've launched the Hyundai harness
all different kinds of Hyundai harness
just go to the website the compatibility
flow now works first order to Hyundai
vehicles
yeah we launched the comma key which
allows you to unbreak - comma - like
conveniently plugging them in we have
the common jungle it works for the an
Ikea and Genesis on forgetting things I
should tell these things these work for
young guys Kia's and Genesis so if you
have a Hyundai or Kia or you happen to
live in Saudi Arabia and Ola Genesis
these things are perfect for you what
are the best Hyundais I love my 2020
Hyundai Sonata it's really a great car
business is business is booming so we
need sixty nine thousand dollars
yesterday selling pandas we're hiring a
lot of people this year - welcome to the
big year of expansion you see this is
Zuke's
this is ok so that's good if you guys
are interested comedy I slash jobs with
a beautiful office here in San Diego
guys can come join it's a nice office so
nice forgive everybody like you know how
like the tech companies are like
cramming people in it like you get a
little like you get a little desk and a
shared office we have like a real nice
like everyone is like 100 square feet of
space everyone's got lots of space what
about interns a new job posting for
Executive Assistant well that's exciting
um how many employees now we're like 15
we have interns how much is the rents
the 13 km um
how is security considered what how did
you throw me into reading that um this
gender I have more experience work than
Toyota it's similar
I haven't had torque problems yeah
it's a lot better than Honda I'll say
that well I pay for relocation yet we
have relocation bonuses
what about entry-level jobs not really
common to repair program if you're calm
and choose broken they're all still
under warranty it's uh we have a
one-year warranty I almost of course you
like dropped it we don't drop it
but yeah or we also have a 30 day no
questions asked money back guarantee on
anything bought in our store so if you
buy something you don't like it doesn't
work with your car to send it right back
you own your money back do you let your
employees anyone's welcome to work from
home ah but I don't know I mean I like
coming to the office um is it made in
America yeah it's been right in the back
it's made right in the back down here in
San Diego I swear we're not Mexico um
well don't make false claims about
coronavirus we'll get booted off YouTube
I need more data scientists maybe then
we don't like like if you're just a data
scientist probably not but if you can
code well and you want to analyze data
yeah yeah we got a lot of data analytics
we got to do
it'll be more globally targeted I don't
even know what that means you're the
same guy who asked about security
if you're looking for the executive
assistant job we're looking for people
with really like experience in that sort
of role we're trying to grow come a lot
this year
like operationally we're trying to go to
20 people by the end of a year now is a
great opportunity
you know guys you know the old saying
it's like step one become worthy step to
accept power step three rule we're still
working on step one but step two has
never looked more closed so that's
really exciting do we take paypal maybe
I'm not sure maybe you can check out
with PayPal flex raise over no remote
work yeah a flex rate flex rate no flex
right not gonna happen
do we accept Bitcoin no I don't think so
just sell your Bitcoin and you know buy
it with a normal credit card how about
how are sales doing
24-hour bodyguard mean no oppai CVE
if you can find bugs just file them on
issues if you have like a real security
issue you can email me um is there a map
of comma users we are everywhere Wow
total sessions you guys I see you on the
website I see you just thinking about
making up your mind about whether you
want to buy it for another 15 minutes
you can save $1 when on IR any marketing
people get out of here with your
marketing boo boo marketing no flex rate
harness is not for sale
no we were we focus on late ok guys just
look come on our shopping you know walk
on the shop page we'll go we'll do
computer together go on the shop page
and I want you to look at how far we've
come
you know so the what are the jungle and
the key really the jungle is really
replacement for the debug board right
compare this product which is like three
traces on a two layer board to this
crazy thing all right like that's how
far calm has come in the last two years
Mahindra Scorpio guys back huh
who's ever Manning the YouTube can we
can we can we can we yeah change the
order of the products yeah we might
we're gonna change up the store a lot I
think giraffes are going away bye-bye
giraffes nobody's gonna miss you you
were the shittiest product comment ever
made alright Mahindra Scorpio is a funny
joke it's fine um you only said it once
but if you say it more than once yeah
the comic he compared the comma key to
the panda paw wow this is like something
like look at that look at this
engineering this is like look at look at
that caught on the board ooh
it's terrible look at the comma key
beautiful it's beautiful it's comma
crime worth it yeah kind of depends
guys how's that the unde I posted going
we have those who died things posted up
somewhere you only come back down Oh C
or D refer to the image I don't owe you
some one DM me and told me that I leaked
it one of the discount codes there was a
tiny minute when you could have saved
the hundred dollars with a discount code
and then we would have been validated
your order
um can I share that sheet yeah we're
gonna share the sheet will share the
sheet when we're done
are you fund a great journey with Prime
no prob out like Prime is what it is
it's an unlimited the SIM card for your
thing I like it but I don't really care
about the money so you know but if
you're trying to like like penny pinch
and save money conference probably not
ready yet the big thing that's gonna
complicado prime is navigation so the
real reason that we smoke weed at the
office what do you think this is the
what was I saying I got distracted
talking about the Hyundai harnesses Oh
navigation yeah comma crime with
navigation that's right um if you have
come crime you're gonna need that in
order to get navigation to get navigated
an open pilot navigate an open file it's
gonna be like a phone comma experience
it's gonna be pretty cool uh and of
course you know prices only go up oh
yeah we raised a price today we raised a
price today so we used to sell these
wires these harness connectors for $50
they used to be only $50 but now thanks
to the insane complexity of Hyundai we
were actually losing money at $50 so
they're now $100 for all of them you're
not good at any of those can you still
get a job no
best way is to close this stream and
purchase things with discount code
livestream 100 it would be for Honda
John died in that way we have great
stuff for Honda tab I don't care what
degrees you have you're gonna come in
here and you're gonna we're gonna ask
the following question do you say smart
things and you not say stupid things so
as long as those two things are true
you're probably pretty good and you got
to know things right so you know when I
ask you questions like what's the output
space for segments you better know right
what's categorical cross-entropy let's
go let's go
hey following distance your following
distance is just social distancing for
your car's floor gang I believe before
gang chill the floor for bed oh you
always playing with us playing with this
lady go yesterday no support for the
Mahindra Scorpio there are great offline
navigation apps why needing Kama Prime
no not for ours what it's gonna be
does the compa to make sure you're
paying attention to the road yes it does
yes it does it has driver monitoring
even at night powered by infrared LEDs
so I'm number one car makers you look at
to get the best experience right now the
out-of-the-box best experience is the
2020 Toyota Corolla though if you're
thinking for the future I have one we're
gonna work on it really hard the 2020
Hyundai Sonata is gonna be a great car
it's already supported right now for
long offer for lateral its longitudinal
policy is better than Toyota's let's
just say that no navigation in Europe
then yeah probably America only yes it
watches the eyes and it watches the head
position just come from allow remote
access come to cameras in the vehicles
parked absolutely yes so that's that's
in the app when you click on the device
it'll take snapshots it's great you know
my car got totally ago and it was great
get out of here with the hacking and
exploitation stuff
we're talking about we're here to talk
about comma if you cover up the camera
will still work with steering wheel
nudges yes it will yes if you really
don't like driver monitoring you can
fall back to the the Tesla like mode of
nudging the wheel but I think driver
moaning is a lot better yeah coming in
five weeks that's awesome
tell us about navigating on paths like
navigating on autopilot gonna be shitty
here for you everything we're gonna get
better than them because we're sick
crazy machine learning ideas that's
beyond the Tesla house does it check if
you are drunk don't drive drunk what
comments for traffic light recognition
that's the wrong way of thinking about
it will it stop at traffic lights that's
a better way of thinking about it think
end-to-end guys you got a thing fourth
dimensional II yeah you're driving from
New York California enjoy man gonna be
fun drive traffic lights Awards comma
recognition that's enough talking about
right now that's stupid vehicle to
vehicle communication is extremely
stupid and vehicle to infrastructure
communication is only slightly less
stupid except that's what comma Prime is
so make sure to buy comma crime if you
have stuff all right for anyone just
joining the stream today we launched a
common jungle Panda jungle panda jungle
is there a public road map you'll find
some stuff in the github if you look
around is driver monitoring video stored
in the TV not by default by default we
do not record it at all
but you can opt into an optional in
settings but if you just install it
straight up now it's not by default it's
entirely local to device what's
virtually Christine virtually Christa's
are head of communications he is our
head of communications who was the worst
employee you've ever had you really
think I'm gonna answer that I do have
one in mind um
did Andres talk prove to you that you
were ahead yeah yeah we're ahead of
Tesla machine right we're ahead of Tesla
machine learning Tesla is ahead of us
and hardware and obviously have us a
fleet I see this alex work at Commodore
Alex was a seasonal employee at comma oh
by the way you can also use your panda
jungle with a black panda or a comma -
you get so many choices you can even go
crazy you know I don't know where the
wire so here's another one of these USB
fires you take this USB wire and you can
plug in both blind spot integration
coming soon ah you can plug in both a
comma 2 and a black panda into your
panda jungle and you can only unlock the
comma two with a comma key of course the
Panda uses a pan of pong it's all very
straightforward and clear what is driver
monitoring do it beeps or does it tell
you to pay attention to the road it
tells you it watches you and if you're
not paying attention it tells you to
look at the road and then if you don't
look at the road for long enough it
stops accelerating it's all level to man
it's all level two features over
bugfixes boo bug fixes over features yay
yeah we love fixing bugs fixing bugs is
our favorite thing to do to ever get a
ride one of the gimmicks cristinaw ain't
give me all right so you know maybe it
was the scam um yeah yeah yeah we'll get
we'll get those blind spot monitors
integrated that's gonna happen that's
still not gonna be autonomous lane
change it's just gonna block the lane
change if there's something in the blind
spot is 0.5 I would be released to next
week um do we have pipelines we got
big-ass pipeline in the garage yeah how
do we support any trucks I think we
support the Honda Ridgeline is that a
truck yes it is a truck let's see I
think we support the new Ridgeline no we
don't support thank you Oh check out my
large Dunkin Donuts iced coffee
Oh banger free doughnuts even better I
hate to eat dogs yesterday though no gas
pedal disengage will not be optional you
don't get out of here with that Tesla
beating hardware in 2020 I don't even
know what that means
surround monitoring with yeah it
functions dash cam if functions dash cam
it's all integrated with the common
connect app it's pretty nice when will
we get our L to actually work we're
using our out the new models you can
take the lanes out of him and they still
drive pretty well the internet update is
fixed to the nearest six five zero seven
five I'm sorry about that it's fixed but
leave virtually crystals a Honda Civic
but I'm not sure about that you'll have
to ask him yeah so we're coming close to
three o'clock where our great live
stream one discount code expires
it does work with a face mask with
sunglasses just us what hours do I work
non-stop
I heard elan name the baby influenza
musk how does it interact with the
heads-up display I mean I don't know
I've never used this in Ottawa thout I
used it very briefly with the stock
system and the stock system did some
weird stuff that I didn't understand and
then I put in well I didn't put it in be
great hard-working people of kamma put
it in and do I think Tesla could change
the AI approach of coma yeah maybe but
not everyone of that organizations on
board with that
kradic knows what's up how many cameras
did it have this two cameras it's the
comic - so it has two cameras it has one
camera right here looking out at the
road that's solid driving camera what is
my point of an address get out of here
and it has this camera which watches you
the driver monitoring camera what is the
new product okay a new product is really
the real product that you're gonna want
to buy it's not like a super development
product is the hue of a harness is if
you know dye harnesses are for sale
right here there's five of them there's
gonna be more yonder harnesses than
other harnesses that's how crazy the
hyundai ecosystem is we're here we're
supporting it we got you there software
is pretty good pretty generic so yeah
check it out it's a flat the wrong
nobody cares about you um guys I don't
know I think Hyundai is gonna be our top
car soon
what is the coupon code do live stream
one you could save $1 what resolution
you're asking the wrong question it has
way more resolution than it needs we
downsample the pixels you want big
pixels you don't need big resolution so
gonna be a new hardware after you
release the softball so this is 1.0
hardware so we're gonna get the comet to
to go all the way to 1.0 this is why
like we have a one-year warranty on this
product you know the Aeons some of them
kind of broke especially if you left
them in the car comma two should not
break they're really well tested so yeah
this is 1.0 hardware so this is gonna be
this is gonna get us the 1.0 software
what's released except Hyundai harness
if you have a Hyun died you can get a
yunda harness what I merge with test
ah I thought about it a little but now a
new bundle of images you got to figure
out the old ones yeah chill for comment
m'kay
if you guys want to go fill out thingies
go comet and cake who's designing the
hardware right here in the house we got
an amazing hardware team yo good
describe yeah it's a great meme I love
this does it work in right-hand-drive
countries yes it does zero seven five is
going to support right-hand drive it
actually puts in a bit to the model that
tells it yo stay on the other side of
the road we worked really hard on that
it's a toggle in the settings I'm here I
can just bring it up paranoid on my eon
let's go to my eon here and right here
you can just toggle and it says enable
right hand drive that also makes the
driver monitoring look out the other
side too
so it's pretty crazy Hyundai harness is
live W harness you guys are always
asking for the next thing you know maybe
maybe a webby next week we'll do the VW
on us does that mean you guys happy um
but yeah check this out yeah one about
0.75 here that's it right here so just
any yarn did I fix the metric system
option was it broken if it's broken yeah
we'll definitely fix it I don't know I
don't know what broken pencils going
pretty well
that's come pretty well talking about a
new segment one of our car manufacturers
next to be included so let me see the
picture I have a picture and I think
I don't know was it in devil come oh yes
yeah here we go
so guys this here is all the supported
cars we support them all now every
single one in green we have at least one
bottle supported by the car and what's
wrong with the red and what's wrong with
the yellow who knows what's wrong with
the yellow
nope I don't even think Mahindra is on
this list actually I've never even heard
of them why our car harness is $200
they're gonna be 300 soon so I buy it at
200 be like damn that was a good deal no
what's wrong with the yellow ones who
knows what's wrong with the yellow cars
we have the link in the Mazda and the
Ford 10 second time out exactly so those
cars have timeouts so you can't control
the steering wheel for more than 10
seconds at a time
what's wrong with the red ones who knows
what's wrong with the red cars
nope flex yes the red cars have flex
right now flex race supports never gonna
happen so we've actually supported all
the cars that we can that's every that's
this is these are car sold in America
that's like every brand
yeah the business is going to vigils
going crazy you know you guys so I
posted the sales numbers on Twitter
yeah so you guys remember you know
remember when I did that livestream
where we just like uh you know
complained about how terrible everything
was that was our sales numbers after
that how crazy is that I misspelled Jean
dye your meetings right there
and I I spelt it right young died yeah
yellow yellow cars are a week no it's
not even stock diem what's light green
versus dark green um I think light green
we don't actually support any of them
but there's no reason we can't shun died
Sunday I don't know but yeah so you know
things are going things are going really
well
alright everybody hit that thumbs up
button on this YouTube video right now
could we get a hundred thumbs up a part
of it ecosystems not open-source so
hardware is not open source because open
source benefit hardly a hundred and five
well that was so fast open source
hardware doesn't benefit 122 that's
crazy
124 um open source hardware doesn't
benefit anybody except for the you know
the knockoff maker self not really
looking to help them out we're looking
to help you out you the individual
person car companies will start to try
to lock me out oh my god I get this
question all the time Apple tried to
lock me out so he tried to lock me out
and they tried real hard you think you
know this is this is this an egg no it's
in it's in it's in forgot about Dre you
know when he's talking about his guns
people running around talking and saying
about guns like I ain't got no and
what you think I sold them all cuz I
stay well off what you think I forgot
how to hack you think they're gonna stop
me nobody's gonna stop me nobody's gonna
stop Karma AI we are unstoppable
we're actually I'm stoppable I mean you
know what I mean like they could shut
this whole thing down they could bring
this whole didn't bring this whole
building down they can put me in jail
and comma is unstoppable because open
pilots open source software and you
can't stop the speech you can't stop the
flow of information oh yeah um what if
they put on Ford like lockouts yeah but
it would also apply to them and that's
the
problem and honestly could I figure out
how to reflash the fort yes do I care -
no it's for hire new people
yeah well hire new people they're still
Lincoln for 20 yr people get on commie
and I slash jobs apply can the model
still work without a radar almost we're
so close
we're so close to - ray darkness ah
Oh what if they getting encrypted oh no
where they're gonna put the key oh the
key oh it's gonna be so hard to find I'm
gonna have to dig deep can't I
longitudinal support like next one two
months what about selling your own
powered steering - garages what you can
just buy it yourself it's super easy to
install it takes five minutes a harness
also open-source yetis things are
open-source we posted them all okay guys
thank you all for joining there's never
been a better time to join the comic
ecosystem how many can die harnesses
have been sold
same ones same aah Oh No six-six yun
dialysis yeah how many suru zero there's
no advise me super ten they make changes
politically yeah they can stop me but
are they gonna stop the the unlimited
flow of comas from China but you know
there's no reason to stop me you're here
we're out making driving better we're
I'm making driving safer we're out
making driving kill that's our slogan
make driving kill just the warranty
cover theft no okay you should have
stolen um ask about the window manager
gonna get banned uh we come in other
countries no the warranty doesn't cover
you drop it no you can't drop it but it
covers manufacture defects if you have
any problem and you use it normally then
um we're happy to help you what is uh
okay all right all right all right thank
you all for watching everybody go buy a
Hyundai harness young guys are the new
officially supported cars we support
Honda's Toyota's young guys and a whole
bunch of other a kind of unsophisticated
I our Honda's Toyota's and our latest
yonder you think I would build who did
we build all these harnesses if if we
didn't care deeply about Hyun diet we do
is the car list online yeah commodore
guys often pilot
check it out know the training all the
trainings all closed source the
trainings all secret guys you know what
about the training like we could open
source the training and unless you have
a half-million-dollar supercomputer and
can't run any of it at myself it would
only benefit zooks
and you know Wow Zeus
[Music]
but comma whoo all right
no flexure will not give any profits
flex raise the biggest rabbit old
flexure is worse than Subaru
yeah actually those are really nice cars
but sorry we're not sporting flex a
Mahindra hi we're gonna look into this
Mahindra Colombo whatever it is does it
work in UK yeah it works everywhere now
we support right-hand drive so we got
everywhere on his Greyhound bus support
coming Subaru works so well but nobody
uses it because like guys think your
average Subaru driver take your average
fee on that driver yeah now we're
talking get in Hyundai drivers today is
a perfect day to get in through the
common community and purchase stuff what
happens 1 million or July we'll get
there we'll get there we'll get there
all right thank you all for watching
they'll never stop us yes the driver
modern filter view does work with the
right-hand drive you don't want it I'll
be Hyundai 500 tota well I hired zukes
employees absolutely yeah yeah yeah
absolutely
if you worked at Suk's and you see the
air on your ways nice this is a cool
company I should rip on Zeus too much
good on them when putting those videos
out and I hope they uh you know what you
want to start being honest about
everything they put those videos out
where they have engineers talking over
an hour that's beautiful thank you thank
you that's being honest you want to talk
about your cruise origin on stage get
outta here get out of here it's the
current year we no longer tolerate that
a born-again suit just come to come
I come join the winning team for
self-driving cars right here in good old
San Diego all right thank you all for
watching goodbye